So, I was able to dig up from 2005. He
would have been 14 or 15 years old.
Not bad. This has to be around the time
for [music] Earl made in my mind. But
that chord for sure, seventh chord on a
synth is so Tyler. Literally never goes
away in his entire career. So, I did
find one of his earliest albums. It's a
EP called Stereotype.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> So, I don't know if it was like his
producer name or what, but he also had a
alias called Polymono. Have you heard of
this at all?
>> No.
>> Poly/Mono, I think was either another
character or alias, or it was his
producer name because he released this
project called Pink Gold Square Pixels.
>> Okay, I'm [__] with this.
>> That's good. You can start to get the
darker.
You can hear some like Odd Future ramped
up vocals to this.
>> Yes.
>> [laughter]
[music]